{
    "id": "d2101389e30f45cfa510198249083837",
    "title": "Reported Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I told him ………………… interfere with me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to not",
                "not to",
                "to don't"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked me ………………… at once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "to leave",
                "that I leave"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him if he …………………. finished the work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked us ………………… on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to be",
                "for being"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked if he …………………. leave early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They asked me ………………….. joining them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that I was",
                "if I was",
                "if I am"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. me to come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "asked",
                "asked me"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ………………. anything from him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hasn't heard",
                "hadn't heard",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She told me …………………. she wasn’t coming.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "why",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him what ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was his problem",
                "his problem was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}